Finding Aid of the Woman's Club of Wisconsin Records, 1870-2012
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Woman's Club of Wisconsin Records, 1870-2012
Woman's Club of Wisconsin
UWM Manuscript Collection 221
Accession 2010-059
Accession 2012-045
27.3 cubic ft. (32 boxes) 2 oversize folders plus additions of 1.6 cubic ft. (3 boxes)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
This collection contains records from the Woman's Club of Wisconsin and the affiliated organizations of the Athenaeum Stock Company, the Guardian Realty Stock Company, the League of Patriotic Women, and the Woman's Club of Wisconsin Foundation, Inc. The records mainly consist of correspondence, meeting minutes, committee files, legal papers, architectural drawings, programs, newspaper clippings, newsletters, yearbooks, and photographs of the club and its members.
The Woman's Club of Wisconsin was created in 1876 by a group of woman looking to enrich their lives with various social, intellectual, and philanthropic pursuits. They established the second club of its kind in the United States, the first being the Woman's Club of New England. In addition to this accomplishment, these founding women also created the very first all-women's stock company in the country. According to its mission statement, "The Woman's Club of Wisconsin is a private club providing its members with philanthropic, cultural, educational, and social activities. The club is dedicated to the support of, and involvement in, community service. The club is also committed to the preservation of its registered landmark building."
The collection includes many of the documents that went into celebration of the club's 125th anniversary in 2001, which led to the creation of the book, A Club of Their Own. This book chronicles the club's history and gave birth to the project undertaken by the history committee to gather and organize the club's records so that members of the club, as well as the community, can have access to the history of this pioneering organization. A Club of Their Own, is available in the Archives. Call number: (ARC) HQ1905.W6 T88x 2000.
Scope and content notes of each series are included in the contents list.
This collection was received in, and is organized in, multiple parts. Additional materials have not been physically or intellectually arranged and interfiled, and researchers may need to consult more than one part of the collection to locate similar materials.
The collection is arranged into the following subgroups:
The Athenaeum, 1886-1964
Guardian Realty Company, 1924-1936
League of Patriotic Women, 1917
Woman's Club of Wisconsin, 1870-2012
Woman's Club of Wisconsin Foundation, Inc., 1961-2004
The files are organized alphabetically by subject, then chronologically, within each group.
The collection contains two additional accessions.
Accession 2010-059: Additions, 1980-2001
Accession 2012-045: Athenaeum Board Meeting Minutes, 1893-1919
Finding aid for accession 2010-059 available in the Archives.
Related Material in the UWM Libraries
Albert J. Earling Papers Milwaukee Manuscript Collection BP
Deaccession Information
Floral prints (removed from box 21) were returned to the Woman's Club of Wisconsin in October 2010.
Administrative/Restriction Information
There are no access restrictions on the materials, and the collection is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
The Woman's Club of Wisconsin donated this collection to the Archives in December 2004 (accession 2004-040). The Club donated additional materials in April 2007 (accession 2006-055), June 2008 (accession 2007-067), and April 2010 (accession 2009-055). The Milwaukee County Historical Society donated Club materials, deaccessioned from its holdings, in February 2010 (accession 2009-045). The Club donated additional materials in June 2011 (accession 2010-059) and James Henderson donated additions in March 2013 (accession 2012-045). Valerie McDonald donated additions in April, 2014 (accession 2013-044).
Contents List
- Records, 1870-2012, UWM Manuscript Collection 221; 27.3 cubic ft. (32 boxes) 2 oversize folders
  - 1. The Athenaeum, 1886-1964
    The Athenaeum is the name of both the clubhouse building and the first stock company. Originally called the Pioneer Woman's Stock Company, it was later renamed the Athenaeum Company. This was the first all-woman's stock company in the United States, and was formed in 1886 to raise the funds needed to build the clubhouse. It was originally created as a separate entity from the Woman's Club of Wisconsin (WCW) with its own board of directors. All groups interested in using space within the building did so through the Athenaeum. In 1920 the Athenaeum formally merged with the WCW, but the name was still used for renting the building to outside clubs and parties. This subgroup includes photographs of the building and the first president, Martha Fitch.
    - Articles and By-Laws, Annual Reports, 1888, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Articles of Association and Minutes, 1886-1893 (Box 1, Volume 1)
    - Board of Directors, Meetings, 1907-1912 (Box 1, Volume 2)
    - Deeds and Title to the Athenaeum, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Histories of the Athenaeum, 1897, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Legal Documents, Transfer of the Athenaeum to WCW, 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Lists of Receptions, Parties, and Cotillions, 1888-1893 (Box 1, Volume 3)
    - Martha Fitch
      - Speeches Given to Board of Directors, 1886-1890 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Speeches Given to Woman's Clubs, 1890, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Formation of the Athenaeum Company, 1923, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Photographs of Athenaeum, 1888, Bound volume of exterior views of the building and interior views of rooms and furnishings. (Box 1, Volume 4)
    - Photographs of Athenaeum, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Stock Certificates, 1886-1893 (Box 1, Volume 5)
    - Stock Certificates, 1893-1920 (Box 1, Volume 6)
  - 2. Guardian Realty Company, 1924-1936
    The Guardian Realty Company was the second stock company formed by the club. Created in 1924, its purpose was to raise money needed to purchase several properties surrounding the club in preparation for future expansion. The clubhouse addition was completed in 1936, and in February of that year Guardian Realty was dissolved. This subgroup mainly consists of financial and legal materials.
    - Correspondence of the Corresponding Secretary, 1924-1936 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence of the President, 1926-1936 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Financial Statements, 1924-1936 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Legal Documents
      - Abstract of Title, Lots 11 and 12, 1835-1935 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Contractors, 1932-1936 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Deeds, Titles, and Mortgages, 1924-1936 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Stock Certificates, 1924, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Stockholder Lists and Meetings, 1924-1935 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Stockholder's Meeting Minute Book, 1924-1936 (Box 2, Volume 7)
  - 3. League of Patriotic Women, 1917
    This league formed in 1917 in response to the United States' entrance into World War I. The Woman's Club of Wisconsin invited all the women from various clubs in Milwaukee to join them in March of 1917 to form the league. Soon after the league merged with the National League for Women's Service, which was based in New York City. Records include information on the first meeting and the formation of the league.
    - First Meeting Invitation and Notes, March 7, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - List of Participating Organizations and Copy of Telegram Sent to President Woodrow Wilson, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Formation of the League, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 4. Woman's Club of Wisconsin, 1870-2012
    The Woman's Club of Wisconsin has a board of directors consisting of a president, several vice presidents, corresponding secretary, recording secretary, treasurer, and members-at-large. In addition to the records of the board of directors and many committees and sub-committees, this subgroup, which makes up the bulk of this collection, contains materials documenting the club's history, activities, and programs; finances; building, including architectural drawings; and membership. Also included are newsletters, yearbooks, and photographs.
    - Articles of Incorporation and By-Laws
      - Constitution, and Printed By-Laws, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - General Club Organization, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Policies, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Revisions, 1976, 1996, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors
      - Annual Reports, 1961-1981 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence, 1923-1927 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1932-1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1987 (Box 4, Folder 6-8)
      - Correspondence, 1978-2001 (Box 22, Folder 3-16)
      - Manuals
        - Committee Chairs, 1988-1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
        - President and Club Manager, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
        - Treasurer/ Finance Chair, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
        - Vice Presidents, Secretaries, and Member-At-Large, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Meeting Menus, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Members of the Board, 1981-1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Minutes, 1876-1884 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Minutes, 1887-1955 (Box 4, Folder 15-27)
      - Minutes, 1956-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1-20)
      - Minutes, 2001-2004 (Box 31, Folder 9-10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966, undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Protocols, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Report to the Board, 1948-1951 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Club History
      - Anniversary Celebrations
        - 50th
          - Photographs, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - 75th
          - Yearbook, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 20)
        - 100th
          - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 21)
          - Planning, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 22)
          - Photo Album, Centennial Celebration, 1876-1976, 1976 (Box 27)
          - Program, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 23)
        - 125th
          - Anniversary Art Photographs, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 1)
          - Anniversary Celebration Photographs, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 2)
          - Anniversary Certificate of Recognition from Senator Feingold, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 1)
          - Commemorative Book "A Club of Their Own" Development and Marketing, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 16)
          - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 24)
          - Sculpture Project, 2001-2012 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Bank Vault Information, 1944-2004 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Book Plates, undated (Box 22, Folder 26-27)
      - Brochures, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Founding and Organizing, 1876-1899 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Founding and Organizing, Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Historical Information (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - Histories, Club Member Recollections, 1920-1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Histories, Printed/Published, 1886-1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Menus, Weddings, Dinners and Events, 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - Newspaper Clippings, circa 1900 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1920s-1980s, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4-7)
      - Scrapbook, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - Stationary, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Committees
      - Activities
        - Antiques Study Group, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - Art
          - Committee Description, 1979-1992, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
          - Correspondence, 1882, 1892, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
          - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
          - Exhibits, 1970s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
          - Exhibits, Insurance, 1979-1988 (Box 6, Folder 14-16)
          - Folk Handicraft Exhibits, French, 1920 (Box 6, Volume 9)
          - Folk Handicraft Exhibits, Greek, 1920 (Box 6, Volume 10)
          - Folk Handicraft Exhibits, Italian, 1920 (Box 6, Volume 11)
          - Folk Handicraft Exhibits, Japanese and Chinese, 1920 (Box 6, Volume 12)
          - Folk Handicraft Exhibits, Romanian, 1920 (Box 6, Volume 13)
          - Folk Handicraft Exhibits, Russian, 1920 (Box 6, Volume 14)
          - Folk Handicraft Exhibits, Scandinavian, 1920 (Box 6, Volume 15)
          - Folk Handicraft Exhibits, Yugo-Slavic, 1920 (Box 6, Volume 16)
          - Member Lists, 1970-1995, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
          - Minutes, 1972-1989 (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
          - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
          - Photographs, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
          - Toshi Engravings, 1892 (Box 6, Folder 22)
        - Book Club, 1997-2002 (Box 22, Folder 34)
        - Bridge
          - Committee Description, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
          - Committee Members, 1970-1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
          - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
          - Meeting Minutes, 1975-1988 (Box 6, Folder 26)
          - Meeting Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 12)
          - Reports, 1966-1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
          - Reports, 1973-1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
          - Schedules of Events, 1965, 1981-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
        - Club Services
          - Hospitality Committee
            - Minutes, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 7)
            - Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 8)
          - Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 13)
          - Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 31, Folder 14)
        - Community Projects
          - Minutes, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 19)
        - Coordinator
          - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
          - Correspondence, 1980-1989 (Box 22, Folder 35)
          - Correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box 22, Folder 36)
          - Description of Committee and Members, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
          - Minutes, 1979-1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
        - Drama
          - Minutes, Programs and Reports, 1955-1961, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
          - Newspaper Clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 7)
          - Photographs, 1961, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
        - Education and Enrichment
          - Duties and Member Lists and Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
          - Minutes, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
        - Exercise and Dance
          - Member Lists and Schedules, 1969-1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
          - Minutes and Reports, 1973-1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
        - Fitness and Fun Class, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 37)
        - Garden Club, 2001-2004 (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - Heritage Docents, 1996-1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - Library
          - Chair and Committee Lists, 1936-1968, 1979-1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
          - Minutes, Reports and Correspondence, 1948-1955, 1973-1987, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
        - Social
          - Correspondence, 1973-1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
          - Minutes and Reports, 1927-1946, 1965-1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
          - Responsibilities and Member Lists, 1979-1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
        - Welfare
          - Accepted Applications, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 18-19)
          - Committee Description, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
          - Correspondence, 1957-1968 (Box 7, Folder 21)
          - Correspondence, 1973-1987 (Box 7, Folder 22)
          - Denied Applications, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
          - General Club Information, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
          - Member Lists, 1937-1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
          - Minutes, 1932, 1955-1987 (Box 7, Folder 26-28)
          - Miscellaneous Applications and Forms, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
          - Newspaper Clippings, 1957-1958, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 30)
          - Reports, 1927-1987 (Box 7, Folder 31-33)
          - Vacation School, circa 1899 (Box 7, Folder 34)
        - Zita Style Show, 1986-2001 (Box 23, Folder 4-6)
        - Zita Style Show, 2001-2004 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Ad-Hoc Study, 1976, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Ad-Hoc Study, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - By-Laws, Proposed Changes, 1956-1957, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - By-Laws, Proposed Changes, 1997-1999 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Evaluation, Reviews of Policies, 1977, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Finance
        - Accountant, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 9)
        - Committee Description and Policies, circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 38)
        - Committee Members, 1936-1968, 1977-1978, 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 39)
        - Correspondence, 1936-1981 (Box 7, Folder 40-43)
        - Correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box 23, Folder 10)
        - Finance Policy Handbook, 1978-1985 (Box 23, Folder 11)
        - Financial Summaries
          - Balance Sheets, 1940-1955 (Box 7, Folder 44)
          - General Journals, 1947-1956 (Box 7, Folder 45)
          - General Ledger, 1948-1969 (Box 8, Folder 1-6)
          - Operating Statements, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 7)
          - Treasurer's Book, 1877-1884 (Box 8, Volume 16)
          - Treasurer's Book, 1912-1923 (Box 8, Volume 17)
          - Treasurer's Reports, 2001-2004 (Box 32, Volume 23)
          - Year-End, 1964, 1970-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8-14)
        - Minutes, 1935-1963 (Box 8, Folder 15-19)
        - Minutes, 1964-1990 (Box 9, Folder 1-12)
        - Price Lists, Club Rentals and Dining, 1972-1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
        - Price Lists, Club Rentals and Dining, 1972-1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
        - Revenue Enhancement and Growth Committee Reports, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Focus Group, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - History
        - Archives
          - Committee Description, 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
          - Committee Minutes, 1971-1976 (Box 9, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence, 1876-1923, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 13)
        - Committee Description, 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
        - Committee Meeting Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - History Projects, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
        - Milwaukee Landmark's Commission, 1972-1981 (Box 9, Folder 18)
        - National Register of Historic Places
          - Application Information, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
          - Correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - House
        - Appraisal, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 21)
        - Appraisal, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 22)
        - Appraisal, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 23)
        - Appraisal, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 24)
        - Appraisal, 1968-1981 (Box 9, Folder 25-29)
        - Appraisal, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Volumer 18)
        - Appraisal, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
        - Appraisal, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
        - Appraisal, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
        - Architectural Drawings
          - Eschweiler and Eschweiler, Club Renovations, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 1)
          - Eschweiler, Schneider and Associates, Inc., Club Renovations, 1967-1968 (Oversize 1)
          - George Schley and Sons, Club Renovations, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 2)
          - Various Architects, Club Renovations, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 3)
          - Various Architects, Club Renovations, 1967-2002 (Oversize 2)
          - Various Architects, Club Renovations, 1982, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
          - Window Renovation Project, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
        - Building Renovation, 1977-1983 (Box 23, Folder 14)
        - Clubhouse Window Restoration, 2001-2003 (Box 31, Folder 15)
        - Committee Description and Policies, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
        - Contracts for Repairs to Building, 1949, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 8)
        - Contracts for Repairs to Building, 1971-1988 (Box 10, Folder 9-14)
        - Correspondence, 1965-1994 (Box 10, Folder 15-17)
        - Correspondence, 1995-2001 (Box 23, Folder 15)
        - Cupola Project, 2001-2004 (Box 23, Folder 16)
        - Facilities Planning, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 17)
        - Facilities Planning, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 18)
        - Insurance Policies, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
        - Insurance Policies, 1970s-1980s (Box 10, Volume 19-20)
        - Insurance Policies, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 21)
        - Insurance Policies, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 18)
        - Interior Design Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
        - Maher and Associates Architects, Floor Plans, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
        - Maher and Associates Architects, Program Plan, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 20)
        - Minutes, 1928-1955 (Box 11, Folder 2-4)
        - Minutes, 1986, 1996-1998 (Box 23, Folder 21)
        - Minutes, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous Items, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
        - Negatives of Building, undated, 35 mm safety film negatives (Box 30)
        - Photograph Book for Appraisals, undated (Box 11, Volume 20)
        - Photographs, Miscellaneous of Building and Staff, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
        - Remodel Plans, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 22)
        - Reports, 1955-1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
        - Reports, 2001-2004 (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - Slides of Building, undated, Slides (35 mm) (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Membership
        - Application Lists, 1895-1921 (Box 11, Volume 21)
        - Application Lists, 1924-1964 (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - Application Receipts, 1888, 1931, 1934-1947 (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
        - Committee Policies and Members, 1969-1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence, 1966, 1970, 1980-1986 (Box 11, Folder 13)
        - Correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box 23, Folder 23-27)
        - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - Enhancement and Growth, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 28)
        - Enhancement and Growth Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 32, Folder 14)
        - Membership Applications, 1925-1926 (Box 11, Folder 14)
        - Membership Applications, 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
        - Membership Survey, 1985, 1999 (Box 12, Volume 22)
        - Membership Survey, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 29)
        - Membership Survey, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 30)
        - Memory Book, undated (Box 12, Volume 23)
        - Minutes, 1966-1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
        - Minutes, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - New Member Orientation, 1974-1984, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
        - Non-Resident Members, 1923-1983 (Box 12, Volume 24)
        - Prospective Member Event, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 31)
        - Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - Resident Members, 1923-1936 (Box 12, Volume 25)
        - Samples Application Forms, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
        - Samples Members' Party Menus, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
        - Waiting Lists for Membership, 1964-1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Nominating
        - Committee Description and Members, 1952-1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, 1993-1999 (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Minutes, 1970-1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
        - Reports and Slates of Officers, 1965-1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Planning, Strategic Plan, 1993-1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Professional, Minutes, June 22, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Personnel
        - Reports, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Program
        - Autograph Book of Speakers, 1919-1979 (Box 12, Volume 26)
        - College Endowment, 1975-1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
        - Committee Description and Members, 1936-1994 (Box 12, Folder 11)
        - Concerts, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - Contracts, 1976-1987 (Box 12, Folder 12-15)
        - Correspondence, 1899, 1920, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence, 1964-1987 (Box 12, Folder 17-19)
        - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
        - Events Postcards/Invitations, 1947-1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - Hollander Concert (Chicago Symphony Preview Series), 1979-1987 (Box 12, Folder 20)
        - Mac Dowell Club, Rental of Athenaeum, 1981-1987 (Box 12, Folder 21)
        - Members, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 6)